What up world? This the hottest show ON
THE INTERNET RIGHT NOW. THIS IS NATE
JACKSON. Super funny comedy jam. It goes
down every week in Tacoma, Washington.
Let me introduce you to my comics for
this episode. There they go. My name is
Key Lewis. I'm from Sacramento,
California. What's up? [cheering]
Hey, my name is Cookie Williams. I'm
coming from California representing the
Bay Area.
[cheering]
What's up? IT'S YOUR GIRL PARIS SACHE
REPRESENTING WASHINGTON DC.
WHAT'S UP Y'ALL? It's your boy Ryan
Davis representing Concord, North
Carolina.
>> Hey Jackson, [music]
super funny jam. [singing]
Super [music] funny jam.
Super funny [singing]
jam.
>> We back, baby. It's the comedy jam. Yes
[cheering] sir. We are right here live
in Tacoma, Washington.
This [cheering] where we got East Side
Bloods and Hilltop Crips and like one
Hilltop blood. He mad AS HELL.
WELL, I got to move. [laughter]
Ain't nowhere else to put your shallow
shers full.
We having fun. We in this business a
good look. We got uh we have a gaggle of
white women here I would like to talk
to, but I was in the crowd before. One
of them grabbed my booty on the way by
and then somebody else said he ain't got
no ass. I said we about to talk about
this. I like to wait until we are on
record. So this lady that was in Flavor
of Love, that's Fofy Foofy. She tried to
say I ain't got no ass. Why don't you
stand up and let everybody see that
haircut you got? [cheering]
Hell yeah. That [\h__\h] is trash. Sit your
ugly ass down. Coming in here looking
like a goddamn rooster, [\h__\h]
[laughter] I got cakes. I'm thick. My
mama my mom made a product of Mobile,
Alabama. Look, I ain't going to show
you. But you you was worried when I got
up. You were like, "Is this [\h__\h] about
to?" I would.
Your hair is actually nice. It is. It
is. It It's not from this era, but it is
nice. It's called what?
>> Alipia.
>> Alipcia.
Godamn lady, we filming.
She's like, I'm dying. Like, what the
[laughter] [\h__\h] am I supposed to do with
that?
She said, "I ain't got no ass either. I
lost her in my alipcia fight." God damn.
If you had some ass, I'd want a pizza,
but I can't.
That's crazy. I got to finessa Alipisha
line.
[\h__\h]
Anyway, y'all get up for the main
character from Fifth Element.
[laughter]
The element is love.
Alipe love.
I'm about to start this episode up. Are
y'all ready for the first comedian?
Start making some noise right now.
That's not enough. I NEED MORE NOISE.
MORE ENERGY. MORE NOISE. MORE ENERGY.
All the WAY FROM THE BANK. Y'ALL GIVE IT
UP FOR KEITH LEWIS.
[cheering]
We live in a society where people are
constantly going around talking about
they got personal issues. My job, my
family, my car. Look at me. Look at this
[\h__\h] You think you got problems? I'm
half black, half white, and I look
Mexican.
>> [\h__\h] y'all. I know what I look like.
Okay, I'm tired of going to Home Depot
on Lowe's and people offering me jobs
and [\h__\h] You know what I'm saying?
It's a tough time to be a black man
trapped in a Mexican body. You
understand what the [\h__\h] I'm saying?
I ain't got no ass. [\h__\h] y'all.
I think we we've been in a space, you
guys, where everybody has a level of
truth. You know, my father, a black man,
raised me by himself, always says, "Son,
living your truth." Your best friend is
not the individual that tells you [\h__\h]
you want to hear. Sometimes your best
friend is the person that post
opposition and tells you [\h__\h] you need
to hear. Do you understand?
If your blood pressure 180 over 120, you
need to take your fat ass to the gym. Do
you understand? And I need people in my
life that are willing to tell me that
truth. You know, he talked to me about
real issues like I was a grown man when
I was 6 years old. Son, since you're the
last down, baby, I'mma tell you
something about life. [laughter]
My father was a bipolar, paranoid,
schizophrenic, aspiring Black Panther
movement pimp. Do you understand me?
A black man. He raised me by himself.
You don't hear about that too much. It's
not a billboard that shows a black man
embracing a little half black, half
white Mexican looking [\h__\h] like
myself. And if you did see that
billboard, you'd be like, "Clearly that
little boy is stolen." cuz that's the
world we live in.
But he taught me [\h__\h] He said, "Son, if
you love a woman and you truly love a
woman, that's the woman you want to be
with. Don't [\h__\h] up your fish show [\h__\h]
trying to get some more [\h__\h] You end
up with no pussy."
[laughter and cheering]
[applause]
I said, "Okay, then I write that [\h__\h]
down on my crayon on my notepad.
Don't [\h__\h] up your for show [\h__\h]
Trying to get some more [\h__\h] You end
up with no [\h__\h] I got it. [laughter]
His
relationship advice molded how I am with
my wife. We've been through a lot. We
make mistakes. I met my wife when I was
15 years old. Latino girl. [screaming]
Yeah.
Gave her a love letter in first period.
This [\h__\h] had a three-month old baby.
That's type relationship. [cheering]
That's racist and true. [\h__\h] y'all.
I think we in a space right now where
truth is very important. You know, we go
through [\h__\h] There's animosity. We far
from perfect, but we together still, you
know,
>> and I be a liar to pretend like I ain't
made mistakes. And that true [\h__\h] rings
out to her. The other day she said some
[\h__\h] to me. She said, "You know what? I
can literally see when you stop
listening."
And I said, "What the [\h__\h] did you just
say?"
Cuz I wasn't paying attention. You know
what I mean? And I'll be honest with you
guys, immediately I was on defensive. I
was like, "What new line of crazy is
this? How the [\h__\h] you see what my ears
are doing?" Right? Ladies and thing, can
you see when we stop listening?
>> Ladies in the back, can you see when we
stop listening? Yeah.
>> So why the [\h__\h] y'all keep talking for
it then?
[applause]
Clearly. You see, WE DON'T GIVE A [\h__\h]
ABOUT WHAT YOU'RE SAYING in that very
moment. But you still keep talking.
Ladies, you got to talk to us when we're
the most attentive. You can't just talk
to us on random times. We got [\h__\h] going
on. I'm a protector and a provider.
That's what I do. I protect and I
provide. And every man in this room,
that would be some [\h__\h] you trying to
do, right? But ladies, you got to talk
to us when we're most attentive. Ladies,
when are men most attentive?
>> After sex.
>> After sex. It can't be after sex. I
ain't never busting nothing about like,
"Let's talk, bitch." Never. I'm ready to
go to sleep, [\h__\h] Get it off me. It's
on my leg. I don't [\h__\h] [laughter]
Your man talk to you after, [\h__\h] I'm
sleeping after.
No, that's right. We do. We a few
minutes.
[cheering]
The last thing my father said, he said,
he said, "Judge, no man or woman
uncommon. Nobody in this room had a
choice about being here. Everybody was
born from somebody. So how can you
criticize or ridicule somebody that did
not have a choice about their initial
existence?" You guys understand that?
>> And I'd be a liar to pretend like I
ain't made mistakes. One of my good
friends recently came out to me. Like he
didn't come out to me in too many words.
He kind of dropped the [\h__\h] on me like a
surprise. He was like, "Keith, how you
feel about two men being together?" And
I was like, "Man, to be honest, it don't
seem natural. I don't see how two dudes
can want to smash one another. And he
said, "Hey man, how come it got to be
about sex? How come two people just
can't love one another?" And that [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] me up. And I realized in that
very moment that he was gay.
And I had to walk the [\h__\h] away from him
cuz I was concerned about all the
homophobic [\h__\h] I may have said to him
over the years. But that's not who I am
as a person, right? So I walked back up
to him. I said, "Hey man, you love me
and I love you, but you not [\h__\h] me."
And he said, "I don't want to [\h__\h] you."
And I said, "You don't want to [\h__\h] me."
[cheering]
Why not?
What's wrong with me? You want to [\h__\h]
me a little bit? Like just the head?
Like, let me get something to make me be
fulfilled as a man.
He said, "I want to [\h__\h] you cuz you
look Mexican and I don't like Mexicans
and I don't speak Spanish." So I was
like, "Fuck you, Miho." You understand?
I've been Key Lewis. God bless y'all. Be
good. [cheering]
Key.
I'm back there cracking up. He like,
"You don't want him to [\h__\h] me?
[laughter] Just make me feel cute. I
ain't I ain't going to go, but I just
just try. JUST GIVE ME SOMETHING to
reject.
>> [laughter]
>> He crazy as hell, man. All right, we
going to go right into the next comic,
man. If y'all ready, start making some
noise right now. More than that. More
than that. More than that. More than
that. Y'all make some noise for Cookie
Williams.
Hell yeah. How y'all doing? [cheering]
Yeah, man. I'm out here chasing my
dreams. This is a dream of mine. I'm
here. Yes.
Yes. [cheering] I EVEN QUIT MY JOB TO
FOLLOW my dreams, you know. Yes. Thank
you. And now I'm looking for a job
because look,
you cannot pay your rent with drink
tickets. I was like, damn. Like I had an
idea and I went through it. I didn't
think it through, you know, cuz nobody
in my family's a comedian. I was like,
man, I want to follow my dream. I want
to do this. I did what everybody else
did. I went to Google. I was like, how
how do you be a comedian? you know, and
they said, "Go to open mic. You get 3
minutes. Go kill it. Somebody going to
see you get added to another show." I
said, "3 minutes?" Like, hell yeah. I'm
about to have some Nate Jackson money.
[\h__\h] this. Like, we doing this? I went
and got on stage. I did a minute and a
half. I got so nervous I ran off. Yeah.
Okay. Maybe I walk fast. But I got up
out of there. You know what I'm saying?
On my way back to my seat, I started
thinking about my ex-boyfriend. I was
like, "Damn, a minute and a half is a
long time." Like, [\h__\h]
I owe him an apology. You know what I'm
saying? I was sweating and breathing
heavy. I was like, I ain't even do no
pumps. I was like, this is this is
crazy. Yeah, man. I got two kids. Yeah.
Yeah.
[applause]
[\h__\h] them. Because look,
my kids do [\h__\h] to get on my nerves on
purpose. I don't know if your kids do
this, but when mine breathe, oh my god,
you got to breathe every day. My
daughter just be in my house smiling,
walking around. I'm like, who told you
you could live here comfortably? Like
that's that's what I want to know. You
know, I had a conversation with my kids
though. I said, "Hey, look, I want to
follow my dream. I'mma quit my job.
I'mma do this. My kids told me that they
believe in me." And I was like, "Hell
yeah." You know, I was like, "We going
to have to take some cutbacks though,
cuz it's, you know, the money not the
same. You know, we going to have to cut
back on a little bit." And my son was
like, "Mom, I know we could cut back on
the food."
I was like,
like, "You being real drastic right
now." Like, I said I said, "Baby steps."
You know? I was like, "I know we could
cut back on Christmas." I was like,
"That's what we going to do this year.
We going to have a reflection Christmas.
It's when you don't get nothing and you
think back to another Christmas
where you got everything you wanted and
then you going to share the story of
that Christmas with everybody else and
that story going to fill you with the
holiday spirit. You know, my son looked
at me, he was like, "Fuck that."
I said, "You know what? I'll go first."
I was like, you know, I was about 7
years old. We had the JC Panty catalog,
nice and thick. You got a brand new pen.
You got to go circle everything you
wanted in that book. It was about a
thousand pages. You got halfway through
that book and realize you wasn't getting
[\h__\h] You circle.
Your parents already has your gifts up
in the closet. They was giving you busy
work. I knew it didn't make no sense
neither. I'm circling lawnmowers and all
type of [\h__\h] Just like I'm just
circling whatever. Like I was like,
"This pen got a lot of ink in it." Like,
you know, I was about Yeah. That was
seven. I had a uh I remember that
Christmas I had a white Barbie doll and
I remember hearing the doll say, "You
know what? She really need a black
Barbie doll." And I was like, "You know
what? My mom white. I really don't care
what color she is. I'm just trying to
get her ready for the club. Like it
ain't [cheering]
it ain't that serious, you know?" And
Chris was coming up. They was like,
"What you want?" I was like, "Man,
Barbie need a ride." You know,
>> and so I asked for a white Jeep. And if
anybody who ever got a car for
Christmas, boy or girl, you know when
you get that car, it come with a
pamphlet full of stickers. Yeah. You got
to have a steady hand to put them
stickers on so you can have a fly paint
job, you know. And I didn't want to mess
up so I let my dad do it. And he put a
bubble in it. I didn't talk to him for
like two weeks. Got Barbie rolling
around here looking crazy, you know.
They surprised me with one more gift. It
was a box the shape of a Barbie box. And
I was like, "Oh, I hope this is a
boyfriend for Barbie." You know, but I
didn't want a Ken doll cuz Ken is gay.
And there's nothing wrong with that.
Just my Barbie wasn't gay at the time.
You know what I'm saying? And when I
opened it, it was a MC Hammer doll. I
WAS LIKE
I was like, "Oh, he fly." He had a
purple suit on. He had a black shirt,
fishnet, and some loafers on with no
socks. I was like, "Oh, this [\h__\h] a
player." You know, if you got the real
one, he came with some gold frames and
then you can't touch this tape. Yeah. I
was like, "This about to be Barbie boot
thing right here." So, I used to put him
in a driver's seat and put Barbie in the
passenger and MC Hammer used to drop
Barbie off at work. And then then he
would take her car and drive it all
around the apartment.
It wasn't until he got two missed calls
from Barbie. He go pick her up
[cheering] and she get in the car all
mad like where you been? Why you use all
the gas? I was like now this a
reflection Christmas right here.
Hey y'all. My name is Cookie Williams
and that's my time. Thank you.
Cookie Williams.
She started playing with the doll in
front of us and then and then and then H
drive around.
>> I love that [\h__\h] So creative, man.
That's what this [\h__\h] is about, man.
Cookie let everybody chill for her kids.
And she was like, "Man, [\h__\h] them kids."
That is hilarious. One more time for
Cookie Williams, y'all.
And we going to go right into the next
comedian. So that clap you got going,
strengthen that. Let's pick that up.
Let's pick that up. Let's pick that up.
Y'all give it up. All the way from
Washington DC, Paris Sache.
[cheering]
God damn it. We here and we gay. We gay.
I'm gay.
Hell yeah. I LIKE THE JOB THEY happy
about gay people. I was going to leave.
This was going to be my last year being
gay. I thought about it cuz they letting
everybody be gay. I don't like it no
more. When I became gay, it wasn't this
gay. People just waking up gay. I'm
like, "Go back to sleep." Nah.
They letting women with five kids be
lesbians.
>> Five kids. Lesbian. That don't even GO
TOGETHER. FIVE KIDS. I DON'T THINK
YOU'RE A LESBIAN. Five kids. You're not
looking for a girlfriend. Five kids. You
looking for help. [\h__\h] you're not
slick.
I'm not watching them kids, [\h__\h] No,
[laughter]
you don't need a girlfriend, [\h__\h] You
need an aunt is what you need, [\h__\h] A
babysitter, [\h__\h] I'm not watching them
kids. No, I got to get a van to date
this [\h__\h] I don't like vans. I don't
like kids. I'm not dating this [\h__\h]
Just want to be gay. I was I was going
to be straight. I googled it. I googled
how to be straight after being gay 7
years.
I said, "Everybody coming out the
closet, I'm going to go back in this
[\h__\h] Let me see.
Let me see how to be straight." I
googled it and Google told me that
straight men are now getting their
assay.
[laughter]
And I said, "That's gay.
I'mma stay the original gay. I came too
far to go back and eat man ass. Are you
crazy? I don't think God created women
to eat man ass. I don't think my Lord
did that.
Women go through enough. I don't think
God ALSO WAS LIKE ALSO EAT MAN ASS.
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
Here's the thing. Every woman in here
has been through A LOT. WE ALL BEEN
THROUGH some [\h__\h] But I don't think no
woman in the world has been through
enough [\h__\h] that you should be on your
knees eating man ass. Absolutely not.
YOU ARE A QUEEN. IT GETS BETTER, [\h__\h]
FIGHT BACK. Stay in it. Believe in
yourself. It's going to turn around for
you and GET UP AND WIPE YOUR LIP. [\h__\h]
I don't like it. I don't even like the
fact that men that get their ass ate is
not a certain look for them. I don't
like that. I don't like the fact men
that get their ass ate look like men
that don't get their ass. They all look
the same. I don't like that. It's no
outer look to see a ass eat a receiver.
I don't like that. We need some type of
look to be like that's a ass eat a
receiver. We need to know. When I do
this joke, all the men laugh. They
trying to blend in. We don't know which
ones. Some [\h__\h] laughing RIGHT NOW.
ASS MOIST RIGHT NOW. [\h__\h] THIS JOKE IS
ABOUT YOU.
I'mma just stay gay. I'mma just stay. I
got tired of it though. I'm sick of it.
Cuz when I became gay, they just made me
the boy. Ain't nobody asked me. Nobody
asked me. They just was like, "You got
the haircut and the Jordans. Get the
check." I was like, "Wait a minute,
[\h__\h] My titties are bigger than yours.
You got the chest, young man.
I think the person with the smaller
titties should pay the bill. You closer
to being a boy, [\h__\h] Get it?"
I hate it. And when people find out I'm
gay, it's like it's no standards. I
don't like that. Girls just find out you
gay and they be like, "Ooh, you gay?"
And I'll be like, "Uh, absolutely not,
[\h__\h] I'm picky with my gay." I ain't
dating no ugly girl. That's crazy. I
date a ugly man if I date a ugly girl.
It's the same thing.
Just want to be gay in peace. That's why
I got a type. I'm picking with my gay. I
got a type. Like I don't like women with
big breasts. I don't like that. That's
not my type.
I got my own titties. I don't need no
more titties. I don't know if y'all ever
seen two women with big titty hug, but
when they hug, they go backwards. All
that all THAT TITTY PRESSURE PUSH YOU
APART. That's not love. That's distance.
I want to love my lady. People with big
titties, they hug sideway. Hey [\h__\h]
Hey [\h__\h] Just
that's too gay for me. I like small
titties. I like like a good A cup B cup.
That's my favorite type of titty.
[cheering]
That's right. I like a good honor roll
titty. That's my favorite type. Don't
bring them big dumb ass titties in my
life. Get your stupid titty gangs away
from me. Stupid titty [laughter] [\h__\h]
Godamn. I just want to be gay in peace.
[laughter]
And I don't hate men. I just think that
they just not smart.
They not. Men think dick can solve
everything. That's the problem. You be
sick. Tell your man you sick. He be
like, "What? You want some dick?" You
like, "I'm sick. I can't even breathe."
He be like, "That's why you need some
dick and tea. You got to sweat it out.
You need some dick and tea." [laughter]
They stupid. Listen, y'all been great.
MY NAME IS PARIS A HAVE A GOOD NIGHT.
>> [cheering]
>> One more time for Paris sach. [music]
She's stupid. She like I'm I'm gay but
I'm picky
cuz I thought that too. I thought like
well if you gay go ahead get all get all
of them then if that's your side get
over there and play. She like this I'm
not all the way over here. Y'all ugly on
this side. She said I make choices and
decisions.
She ain't lying. Men we do think like
whatever wrong with you we can fix with
our dick.
>> [laughter]
>> You like [cough]
you you need some dick.
You need some dick shelter, sir.
You need some dick quill. Get bit by a
rattlesnake. I'm not going to die and a
dick dog. Just
turn up one more time for your boy. We
about to turn up one more time.
[cheering]
Listen, this [\h__\h] is special, man. I
need I need y'all to take it all the way
to an 11 or 12 right now. Start making a
whole bunch of noise right now. And
y'all make some noise for my man 10
grand Ryan Davis. [cheering]
[music]
This year we found out the rapper
Glorilla has a sister brother. Did y'all
say that?
[laughter]
I say sister brother. I don't know what
it is. I just want to [\h__\h] it. Whatever
it is.
Whatever [laughter] it is. I don't know
the pronouns. It's not saying what it
is, but I know it has a vagina. And I'm
trying to be an ally.
[laughter]
I I'm telling you the rules. I'm going
to tell you what I've learned so far.
That the sexual spectrum starts it
straight. Right. And if you deviate from
that, then you get a letter. And once
you get a letter, then you get to go to
the parade. That's the rules. That's
what I've learned so far. And the
parade, the parade, you know, celebrates
the letters.
LGBTQIA+.
That's right. And all the letters
represent how you like to have sex. So,
it's a [\h__\h] parade. And and and the
thing is, I'm trying to learn
everything. Uh, and if it's a [\h__\h]
parade, I don't understand
all the letters. Let me give you an
example. So, it's LGBTQIA+.
You know what the A stand for?
>> No. No. It stands for asexual. That's
right. Not even [\h__\h] nobody. Still
got to go to the parade, [\h__\h] What are
the rules?
How do you even become asexual? Is it
like a choice or like a drought?
You just ain't [\h__\h] nobody in 6 months.
You're like, I got to put a flag on my
car.
>> [laughter]
>> What the [\h__\h] are the rules? And the
plus, I don't understand the plus
because I can't figure out if the plus
is the letters that we already know are
there, but it's too many letters, so we
just shorten it with plus or does plus
represent the letters that we haven't
figured out yet. Like the straight
people, the people in the world who
believe they're straight, but they don't
know it yet because their letter hasn't
dropped.
Like, do you understand how crazy that
is? Like, for example, I'm straight, I
think. But [\h__\h] who knows?
My letter might come out next month.
[laughter]
Now I got to go to a parade. This is
This is an interesting concept.
I went down this rabbit hole. I was
like, "Shit, am I a plus?
I want to [\h__\h] little sister brother. I
might be a plus.
>> [cheering]
>> I was like, I don't know. Cuz you know,
no men, no two men really like the same
thing sexually. You know, one of us is
in the wrong place.
I was like, the only way to figure this
out is if I describe what I like and
describe what they like and see which
one is gay.
This ain't no confession or nothing, but
sometimes [laughter]
my [\h__\h] sound gayer than uh everybody
else's. I'll give you an example. Like
like I look at like I've always been a
straight man. The only thing I care
about is [\h__\h] That's the only time I
love women. That's the only type of sex
I want to have. But I'm going tell you,
I look at other straight men and the
things they're willing to do for [\h__\h]
like they'll they'll grab a woman who's
walking by to harass them. They'll
they'll skip work to try to get it.
They'll spend up all their money and
then I'm like, "Man, I don't like it
that much, [\h__\h] I don't
[laughter]
And if I don't like it as much as other
[\h__\h] sounds kind of gay." It sounds
kind of gay when you don't love it as
much.
[laughter]
Cuz I saw last year I saw the ultimate I
saw the ultimate blood [\h__\h] I've ever
seen. It was a lady on Only Fans who
slept with a thousand men in one day.
Yeah. Slept with a thousand men in one
day. And I know a lot of people was
like, "Man, what kind of woman would do
something like that?" Some people were
like, "What kind of men would do
something like that?" And I was like,
"What letter is that, [\h__\h] You waited
[laughter] for a thousand other people
to Can you imagine sitting on the other
side of the door listening to her have
sex, hear him climax and go, "It's my
time. It's my time, [\h__\h] What letter
is that?" [laughter]
That's why I don't even watch porn no
more, man. Cuz you I don't want to watch
the wrong thing. That's how it happens.
You watch the wrong thing, bam, now you
gay. [laughter]
And I know there's some men in here
that's like, "Nah, you know if what you
watching is gay." I don't know about
that, fellas. I'm going tell you,
there's a lot of stuff out here now.
Like, for example, fellas, let's say you
watching you watching a porn video and
it goes to the next video. You didn't
choose it, but it randomly just went to
it, right?
And the video is of a transgender woman
who still has her penis having sex with
a naturalb born cisgender woman. If you
watch that, fellas, is that gay? H Let's
not all answer at once. I'mma go around
the room and ask every single one of you
[\h__\h] H is it? H
[laughter]
Yeah, [\h__\h] I can see you. H Yeah.
Like, did I jump out there too far for
some of y'all? I I'll reel it in. My
bad. All right. So, let's say if you
watch porn, that means you have a
favorite porn star, right? So, let's say
your favorite porn star is having sex
with two men at once. And these guys
never interact with each other. They
don't touch each other. They don't speak
to each other, man. They don't even look
each other in the eyes. These [\h__\h] is
blindfolded, right? They're just going
half on the torso. They split in a body.
[laughter]
Now fellas, if you watch this lady have
sex with two men who don't interact with
each other at all, is that gay? Hm.
Hm. No. H.
Stop looking at your phone, [\h__\h] I'm
talking to you. H. Is it? Is it? Is it?
Hm. Is it? Hm. See, I'mma tell y'all
something. I'mma tell you something that
you can't see. The point of view that I
have on the first one. Whole lot of Yes.
Yeah, [\h__\h] That's gay. Second one. I
don't know. Nah. Nah. Sounds like a
train to me. You know, a whole bunch of
[cheering]
Which is cool. Which is cool. But that's
when I get confused.
That's when I get confused cuz in one
video there's two sets of titties and
one dick. And in the other video there's
two dicks and one set of titties. Sound
like a lot of you [\h__\h] like dick way
more than you like titties.
I think I found the pluses.
[laughter]
>> Thank you, Tacoma. Y'all dope, man.
[cheering]
Ryan Davis.
Hell yeah. Y'all make some noise for Key
Lewis, Cookie Williams, Paris Sache, and
Ryan Davis.
Thank you y'all. We'll see you next
[cheering] week.
Heat. Heat.